Guide to the 3-D image collection, 1840-2012.
3-D image collection
- Series IV. Lenticular, Holographic, and Anaglyph Processes
  - Lenticular
    - Postcards
      - Space
        - Moon Walkers (Box 30, Folder 178-179)
        - Lunar Descent (Box 30, Folder 180-181)
        - Saturn V Rocket (Box 30, Folder 182-183)
        - Apollo Moon Rocket (Box 30, Folder 184-185)
        - Lunar Ascent (Box 30, Folder 186)
        - Praying Hands & Moon Ships (Box 30, Folder 187-188)
        - Space Ship (Box 30, Folder 189-190)
        - Moon Landing (Box 30, Folder 191-182)
        - Message from Outer Space (Box 30, Folder 193-194)
        - Memo from the Moon (Box 30, Folder 195-196)
        - Space Shuttle (Box 30, Folder 197-198)
      - Miscellaneous
        - Sailing Ship (Box 30, Folder 199-200)
        - Fighting Ships (Box 30, Folder 201-202)
        - Daffodils (Box 30, Folder 203)
        - Flag (Box 30, Folder 204)
        - Roses (Box 30, Folder 205-206)
        - Orchids (Box 30, Folder 207-208)
        - Flag (Box 30, Folder 209)
    - Images & Publications
      - Maker's Mark Whiskey Ad- Xograph (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - Venture Magazine, September 1968 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - Kodak Report Cover (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - 3-D Picture Ad (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - 3-D & 2-Vue Postcard Ad (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Star Trek Mouse Pads (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - Nude Transparency (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - History of Paris Exhibition- 3D (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - Pictorial Productions- 1966 Annual Report, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - Body Voyage Marketing Material, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - Kodak Annual Report- 1965, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - Image Tech 3-D (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - Ducks image (Box 36, Folder 13)
      - Deer image (Box 36, Folder 14)
      - Horses image (Box 36, Folder 15)
      - Spacecraft image (Box 36, Folder 16)
      - Man O' War Ship image (Box 36, Folder 17)
      - Racing Yacht image (Box 36, Folder 18)
      - Whaling Ship image (Box 36, Folder 19)
      - Blinking Christ on the Cross image (Box 36, Folder 20)
      - Christ on the Cross image (Box 36, Folder 21)
      - Christ Praying on Rock image (Box 36, Folder 22)
      - Christ Praying in Garden image (Box 36, Folder 23)
      - Last Supper image (Box 36, Folder 24)
      - Space Hunter Pins (Box 36, Folder 25)
      - Nixon Pocket Calendars (Box 36, Folder 26)
      - Space Xographic Ruler (Box 36, Folder 27)
      - Space Xographic Ruler (Box 36, Folder 28)
      - "Circus" Xographic Stickers (Box 36, Folder 29)
      - "Circus" Xographic Stickers (Box 36, Folder 30)
      - "Pond" Xographic Stickers (Box 36, Folder 31)
      - "Pond" Xographic Stickers (Box 36, Folder 32)
      - Assorted Xographic Stickers (Box 36, Folder 33)
      - "Space" Xographic Stickers (Box 36, Folder 34)
      - Knight image (Box 36, Folder 35)
      - Park image (Box 36, Folder 36)
      - Chicken of the Sea Ad (Box 36)
      - Hallmark Star Trek greeting card, 2009 (Box 36)
      - Christ praying on rock wood-mounted image (Box 36)
      - Devo: Pioneers Who Got Scalped: The Anthology, CD-2472-2473 (Box 36)
      - Body Voyage, 1997 (Box 36)
      - The Bradford Book of Collector's Plates, 1981 (Box 36)
      - "The Lion, King of the Beasts" wood-mounted image (Box 36)
      - "100 Islands, N.Y.": wood-mounted ship image (Box 36)
  - Holographic
    - Equipment
      - Manual and Exposure Calculator (Box 37)
      - Photo Meter (Box 37)
      - Helium Neon Laser Supply (Box 37)
      - 3 Items Wrapped in Paper (Box 37)
      - Large Calipers (Box 37)
      - Various Items -- wires, lenses, 5 red boxes (Box 37)
      - Multiplex Hologram, MU-1459; Mutiplex Company
        A viewer for holographic films. See catalog in box 40.
    - Action Figures
      - Super Naturals ghost figures (5 figures), 1986 (Box 38)
      - Super Naturals action figures (2 figures), 1987 (Box 38)
      - Go Bots (4 figures), 1985 (Box 38)
      - 1 bag misc. unpackaged action figures (Box 38)
    - Images and Publications
      - Hologram Sunglasses -- Dinosaur, Smiley Faces (3 sets) (Box 39)
      - Holographic Coins (Box 39)
      - Holographic Boxes -- Unicorn, Spaceship (2 sets) (Box 39)
      - Lighted Hologram Ornament, 1986 (Box 39)
      - Superman Hologram Cards (6 sets), 1996 (Box 39)
      - Holographic Key chain (Box 39)
      - Neovision Holograms (Box 39)
        5 holograms - charms on chains
      - Toothbrushes with Holographic Sticker (2 sets), 1991 (Box 39)
      - Monsters (book with holograms), 1996 (Box 39)
        Written by Dugald Steer, illustrated by Justine Peek
      - The Skook (book with holographic cover image), 1984 (Box 39)
        by JP Miller
      - Night Stone (book with holographic cover image), 1986 (Box 39)
        by Rick Hautala
      - Captive Caress (book with holographic logo on cover), 1986 (Box 39)
        by Sonya T. Pelton
      - The Devil's Cat (book with holographic cover image), 1987 (Box 39)
        by William W. Johnstone
      - 5 Holographic Notebooks, 1985 (Box 39)
      - Museum of Holography Bookstore Catalog (2 copies), 1983 (Box 40)
      - Museum of Holography Bookstore Catalog (2 copies), 1981 (Box 40)
      - Museum of Holography Bookstore Catalog (2 copies), 1982 (Box 40)
      - Light Fantastic: A Short Guide to Holography (Box 40)
      - Holography (Re)defined: Innovations through Tradition, 1984 (Box 40)
        published by Museum of Holography
      - Multiplex: White-Light Moving Holograms, the Multiplex Company Catalog (Box 40)
      - Shadowgrams: Rick Silberman (Box 40)
      - National Geographic: China's Remote Peoples, Lasers, Holography, Calgary, Rhinos, March 1984 (Box 40)
        Vol. 165, No. 3 (2 copies)
      - National Geographic: World Map, Can Man Save this Fragile Earth?, December 1988 (Box 40)
        Vol. 174, No. 6
      - Holographics International, Number 7, Winter 1989 (Box 40)
      - Publishing Technology: Holograms Burst into Production, July 1989 (Box 40)
      - Sports Illustrated: Sportsman of the Year: Michael Jordan, December 23, 1991 (Box 40)
      - Artforum International, Summer 1985 (Box 40)
      - Things of Science -- Holography (Box 40, Folder 1-2)
      - Assorted "Snorks" Hologram Stickers (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - Assorted Hallmark Hologram Stickers (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - Assorted Hologram Stickers -- 3-Dimensional LTD. (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - Sugar Crisp Rock n' Roll Hologram Stickers (Box 40, Folder 6)
      - Halley's Comet Hologram Stickers (Box 40, Folder 7)
      - Acorn Hologram, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 8-9)
      - Coil Hologram, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 10-11)
      - Micro Kiss # Hologram (Box 40, Folder 12)
      - Crayon Hologram (Box 40, Folder 13)
      - Relativity Hologram Sticker (Box 40, Folder 14)
      - Visacard w/ Hologram (Box 40, Folder 15)
      - Little Fuse Hologram (Box 40, Folder 16)
      - Coins Hologram (Box 40, Folder 17)
      - Bird Reflection Hologram (Box 40, Folder 18)
      - Holographic Art Pin (Box 40, Folder 19)
      - Liberty Holgram Button (Box 40, Folder 20)
      - Lunar Lander Button (Box 40, Folder 21)
      - Space Walker Button (Box 40, Folder 22)
      - Transformers Holographic Pin, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 23)
      - G.I. Joe Holographic Pin, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 24)
      - Grateful Dead Hologram Button, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 25)
      - Rainbow Holographic Pin, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 26)
      - Grateful Dead Hologram Button, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 27)
      - Grateful Dead Holographic Magnet, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 28)
      - Holographic Business Cards, Bookmark (Box 40, Folder 29)
      - Pegasus Card (Box 40, Folder 30)
      - Ship in a Bottle Card (Box 40, Folder 31)
      - Happy Birthday Card (Box 40, Folder 32)
      - Ship Hologram Card (Box 40, Folder 33)
      - Star Hologram Card (Box 40, Folder 34)
      - Star Card (Box 40, Folder 35)
      - Holographic Alphabet Set (Box 40, Folder 36-37)
      - Golden Gate Bridge Hologram Postcard (Box 40, Folder 38)
      - Laser Holograms (Box 40, Folder 39)
      - Misc. Embossed Holograms (Box 40, Folder 40)
      - USS Enterprise Hologram, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 41)
      - Marvel Super Heroes Holograms, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 42)
      - Jet Attack Holograms (Box 40, Folder 43)
      - Unicorn Holograms, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 44)
      - Beast Man Holograms (Box 40, Folder 45-46)
      - Michael Jackson Holograms, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 47-48)
      - Transformers Holograms, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 49-50)
      - The A-Team Holograms, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 51-52)
      - Barbie Holograms, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 53-54)
      - Gremlins Holograms, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 55-56)
      - My Little Pony Holograms, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 57-58)
      - Rainbow Holograms, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 59-60)
      - G.I. Joe Holograms, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 61-62)
      - Skeletor Holograms (Box 40, Folder 63-64)
      - Cabbage Patch Kids Holograms (Box 40, Folder 65-66)
      - He-Man Holograms (Box 40, Folder 67-68)
      - Liberty Hologram, 1986 (Box 40, Folder 69-70)
      - Michael Jackson Holograms, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 71-72)
      - Space Holograms (Box 40, Folder 73)
      - Star Trek Holograms, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 74)
      - Talento #3 Embossed Hologram (Box 40, Folder 75)
      - Embossed Gears Hologram (Box 40, Folder 76)
      - Embossed Holograms (Box 40, Folder 77)
      - Tiffin Holograms (Box 40, Folder 78)
      - Holo-Spectre Hologram of 1st Laser (Box 40, Folder 79)
      - Misc. Holographic Literature (Box 40, Folder 80)
      - Virtual Dialogues -- Hologram Info (Box 40, Folder 81)
      - Holosphere (19 issues), December 1982 - Summer 1989 (Box 16)
      - Scientific American issue, June 1965 (Box 16)
      - Art and Holography, March 1985 (Box 16)
      - Holography Purchase Info, 1985 (Box 16)
      - Publishing Technology, April/May 1989 (Box 16)
      - J.A. Noll Co. Catalog No. 15 (Box 16)
      - Jodon Laser Product Catalog (Box 16)
      - Newport Corporation Catalog 1980-1981, 1981 (Box 16)
      - Newport Corporation Projects in Holography (Box 16)
      - Aerotech Helium Neon Lasers and Accessories (Box 16)
      - Optical Spectra issue, December 1973 (Box 16)
      - Spectra-Physics Helium-Neon Lasers (Box 16)
  - Anaglyph
    - Images and Publications
      - 3-Dimension Entertainment World (Box 17)
      - 3D Movie Magazine (2 issues), September, December (no year) (Box 17)
      - National Lampoon (2 copies), July 1975 (Box 17)
      - Jurassic Park Raptor Attack (2 packets) (Box 17)
      - Nickelodeon Magazine (3 issues), March 2005-2008 (Box 17)
      - Shrek 3-D poster, 2004 (Box 17)
      - 3D Jack Kirby poster (2 copies) (Box 17)
      - 3-D Bat Man (Box 17)
      - Strange Animal Stories (Box 17)
      - 3D Coloring Book: Unicorns (Box 17)
      - Dynamite No. 46 (2 copies) (Box 17)
      - Dynamite No. 78 (2 copies) (Box 17)
      - Image World (2 copies), September/October 1989 (Box 17)
      - Ilford Photo Instructor (2 copies), Fall/Winter 1999 (Box 17)
      - Graphic Arts Monthly, September 1989 (Box 17)
      - National Geographic: Return to Mars (2 issues), August 1998 (Box 41)
      - Discover Mars booklet (Box 41)
        by Gloria Skurzynski, National Geographic Society
      - Reading Lessons and Eye Exercises, 1985 (Box 41)
      - Titanic Ghosts of the Abyss (Box 41)
      - Ready-to-Make Photo & Scene Machines: Antique Optical Inventions Recreated (Box 41)
        by Budd Wentz
      - Amica Mare, 1983 (Box 41)
      - More Secret Origins Super-Villains (Box 41)
      - Look: Pope Paul by his nephew, February 25, 1964 (Box 41)
      - Life: A Baseball Curves but Doesn't Break, Cancan Lingerie, July 27, 1953 (Box 41)
      - Stereovues of New York World's Fair in 3 Dimensions (Box 41)
      - Run Free poster (Box 41)
      - The Werewolf poster, 1978 (Box 41)
      - Star-Gazers Guide, 1992 (Box 41)
      - 2 3Dmt folders (Box 41)
      - Tarzan 3-D Cards (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - Italian 3-D Stamps (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - Honeycomb Anaglyph Posters (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - Adventure in 3-D Set (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - Anaglyphic Cards (Box 41, Folder 5)
      - Seated Woman Anaglyphic Card (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - Macyart Anaglyphs - Electrical Devices (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - "Run Free" Dynamite Poster (Box 41, Folder 8)
      - "The Werewolf" Dynamite Poster (Box 41, Folder 9)
      - "Game Over" Dynamite Poster (Box 41, Folder 10)
      - 3-D Happy Meal - Jungle (Box 41, Folder 11)
      - 3-D Happy Meal - Indians (Box 41, Folder 12)
      - 3-D Happy Meal - Comet (Box 41, Folder 13)
      - 3-D Happy Meal - Moon (Box 41, Folder 14)
      - Booklets of Disney cartoons (Box 41, Folder 15)
- Series V. Toys and Novelties
  - 3D Toys and Books
    - Star Trek Keepsake Ornaments 3-D Puzzle, 1994 (Box 58)
    - Return of the Redeye: The 3-D Puzzle (Box 58)
    - My Tiny 3-D Book Series: Hansel and Gretel (Box 60)
    - My Tiny 3-D Book Series: Snow White (Box 60)
    - My Tiny 3-D Book Series: Cinderella (Box 60)
    - My Tiny 3-D Book Series: Little Red Riding Hood (Box 60)
    - My Tiny 3-D Book Series: Jack and the Beanstalk (Box 60)
    - My Tiny 3-D Book Series: Three Little Kittens (Box 60)
    - My Tiny 3-D Book Series: All About Shapes (Box 60)
    - My Tiny 3-D Book Series: All About Colors (Box 60)
    - My Tiny 3-D Book Series: Nursery Rhymes (Box 60)
    - My Tiny 3-D Book Series: Animals We Know (Box 60)
    - My Tiny 3-D Book Series: Everyday Objects (Box 60)
    - My Tiny 3-D Book Series: Tell Me What Time It Is! (Box 60)
    - My Tiny 3-D Book Series: A.B.C. Book (Box 60)
    - My Tiny 3-D Book Series: All About Opposites (Box 60)
    - My Tiny 3-D Book Series: Mother Goose (Box 60)
    - My Tiny 3-D Book Series: Three Little Pigs (Box 60)
    - 4 A-OK Mini Purses with holographic images (Box 60)
    - Jaws 3D card deck (Box 60)
    - Jaws 3D package - 3-D cards and bubble gum (Box 60)
    - 8 packages 3D stickers with glasses (Box 60)
    - 3D doodle kit (Box 60)
      glasses and holder for dual red and blue colored pencils
    - 2 packages Paas 3-D Coloring Set Easter basket stuffers, 1984 (Box 60)
    - Giant 3-D Fairy Tale Books: Alice's Adventures in Wonderland (Box 60)
  - Kids Novelties & 3-D Colorforms
    - 3-D Baseball Stars (cards), 1985 (Box 61)
    - 3D He-Man Bop Bag, 1984 (Box 61)
    - Muppet Babies 3-D Colorforms Play Set, 1985 (Box 61)
    - Thundercats 3-D Colorforms Play Set, 1985 (Box 61)
    - Golden Girl and the Guardians of the Gemstones 3-D Colorforms Adventure Set, 1985 (Box 61)
    - 3-D Colorforms Play Set (Golden Girl and the Guardians?) (Box 61)
    - Puzzleforms Gremlins Puzzle, 1984 (Box 61)
  - 3-D Electronic Games
    - Tomytronic 3-D holographic decorative board (Box 62)
    - Tomytronic 3-D: Planet Zeon, 1983 (Box 62)
    - Tomytronic 3-D: Thundering Turbo, 1983 (Box 62)
    - Tandy 3-D Electronic Sky Duel (Box 62)
    - Tomytronic 3-D: Sky Attack, 1983 (Box 62)
- Series VI. Movies and Documentaries
  - The Mad Magician, Super 8 F-1096 (Box 34)
  - Creature from the Black Lagoon, Super 8 F-1097 (Box 34)
  - It Came From Outer Space, Super 8 F-1098 (Box 34)
  - Stereo Photography: Places and Times Remembered, VHS V-8920 (Box 34)
  - Sorenson, VHS V-8921 (Box 34)
  - Gorilla at Large, 1982; VHS V-8922 (Box 34)
    Channel 31, Rochester, NY
  - It Came From Outer Space, 1980; VHS V-8923 (Box 34)
  - Creature from the Black Lagoon, 1980; VHS V-8924 (Box 34)
  - Electric Blue, 1981; VHS-8925 (Box 34)
    Pornography